What nuclear war Listen after the Kursk
Какая ядерная война Слушай после Курской
region you can forget about the nuclear war And
области про ядерную войну можно забыть А
what is there in the Kursk region Well that the
что там в Курской области Ну что
territory of Russia was captured and Russia did
территорию России захватили а Россия
not start a nuclear war there, like 500
ядерную войну не начала там типа 500
square meters, that's not the point, that's
квадратных это суть же не в том суть же
not the point, really The point is that the
не в том правда Суть в том что
territory of Russia was captured and Russia did
территорию России да захватили и Россия
not
никак не
respond Hello, finally,
ответила Здравствуйте наконец-таки
Krasnodar, Russia, it's cool Where are you
Краснодар Россия прикольно Вы откуда
from Rostov But I've been living in Poland for 18
родом из Ростова Но живу в Польше уже 18
years, it's interesting I can just see the Polish flag
лет интересно я прям вижу польский флаг
Yes In your background Tell me how you feel about
да На вашем фоне Рассказывайте как вы к
Russians I'm Russian myself I
русским относитесь я сам русский Я так и
understood that the attitude can be different, also
понял отношени может быть разные тоже
Russian How can I be a Russian to treat
русский Как я могу русский относиться к
Russians Well, good or bad Just some
русским Ну хорошо плохо Просто каких
other
другим
people And how do you feel about Russians who
народом А как вы относитесь к русским
support the war
которые поддерживают войну
who supports the war I have a
который поддерживает войну я отношусь
bad attitude Regardless Are they Russian, Tatar,
плохо Независимо Они русские татарские
Chechen, or Ukrainian, or Ukrainian
чеченские или украинские или украинский
Yes, there are a lot by the way, I have a
Да куча кстати есть у меня вот
classmate from Krasnodar, like he
одноклассник из Краснодара типа он этот
supports this Well, he is Ukrainian himself, he has a
поддерживает Ну он украинец сам родом у
grandmother, yes He supports the
него бабушка да Он поддерживает
war again, what is your name Andrey
войну ещё раз как вас зовут Андрей
Andrey, you have a beautiful name and you are in  in
Андрей у вас прекрасное имя и вы в
principle it seems to me that the person is very smart,
принципе мне кажется человек очень умный
wonderful, in fact, they
прекрасный на самом деле
just call you and in principle you
просто зовут и вы в принципе правильные
say the right things, you are great What is your name
вещи говорите вы молодец Вас как зовут
Sergey, well, Sergey Andreevich, actually we
Сергей ну Сергей Андреевич собственно
are saying, I understand, how do you, Sergey Andreevich,
говорим понял как вы Сергей Андреевич
treat
относитесь к
the war fairly or how would I like it
войне по-честному или как бы я хотел сам
personally, how do you treat it
лично как вы
I want it to end
относитесь Я хочу чтобы она закончилось
as quickly as possible It doesn't matter on what
как можно быстрее неважно На каких
terms That is, in principle, if the conditions
условиях То есть в принципе если условия
are such that Russia must give
будут такие что Россия должна отдать
Ukraine also Krasnodar Krai,
Украине ещё Краснодарский край
Rostov Oblast, Belgorod, Kursk,
Ростовскую область Белгородскую курскую
Bryansk, you don't give a damn at all, even
брянскую вам по барабан вообще да хоть
Moscow, it's cool at all Even
хоть Москву прикольно вообще Даже Да
Novosibirsk and so on, only this will not happen
Новосибирск и так далее только этого не
That's the problem
будет Вот в чём проблема К
Unfortunately Well, maybe you followed the
сожалению Ну может вы следили за
previous news correctly And what is
предыдущими новостями правильно И что
there, previous news, today
там предыдущие новости вот у нас сегодня
in Poland, President Donald Tusk said
в Польше президент Дональд Туск сказал
that yes, Europe will send its
что да Европа отправит на Украину свой
military contingent to Ukraine, but
воинский контингент только вот к
unfortunately, to Europe, absolutely the same as
сожалению на Европу абсолютно
to Ukraine Well, in terms of peace
как и на Украину Ну в плане мирных
negotiations Maybe you heard the two
переговоров Может вы слышали две
superpowers are talking about peace
сверхдержавы общаются по поводу мирных
talks stop stop stop stop superpowers stop
перего стоп стоп стоп стоп сверхдержавы
about the superpower, have you seen
стоп насчёт сверхдержавы ты видел
this budget, the GDP of Russia and the GDP of the
бюджет этот ВВП России и ВВП
European Union Yes, of course I have How many
Евросоюза Да конечно видел Во сколько
times  Russia's GDP is
раз ВВП России
probably less than one time Well, if the budget of the
меньше раз наверное Ну вот если бюджет
EU's GDP is 18 times the trinity is correct, and the GDP is Well,
ВВП Евросоюз 18 трино правильно а ВВП Ну
somewhere in ten times with a
где-то в де раз при
10-fold
в 10 раз
difference, Russia's GDP is like the GDP of one
разни ВВП России это как ВВП одной
Chinese province, that is, Russia,
китайской провинции то есть Россия
look, the Soviet Union was a superpower, Russia is not a superpower
смотри Советский Союз был сверхдержавой
at all, that is,
Россия вообще нет сверхдержавой то есть
Russia is not a superpower, but doesn't it
Россия не есть сверхдержава но вам не
seem strange to you that you are asking the question?
кажется странным что вы задаёте вопрос
You say, but what do you think, what kind of What
Вы говорите а вот как вы думаете какая
kind of economic
Вот какой Какая экономическая
component is better for 20 plus countries or for
составляющая лучше у 20 плюс стран или у
one
одной
Ron, it makes no difference at all Tom, a
Роны вообще без разниц вообще Том
superpower, it has no effect on anything
сверхдержавы она ни на что не влияет
Absolutely right, Russia has no effect on anything at all, the
Абсолютно верно Россия вообще ни на что
question is, look at the question If
не влияет вопрос смотри вопрос Если
Russia is a superpower, why can't it
Россия сверхдержава почему она не может
win back its Kursk
отвоевать свою курскую
region Well, because it is very difficult on its
область Ну потому что очень сложно на
own Well, everything is no longer a superpower, a power,
само Ну всё уже не сверхдержава держава
because Yes, of course, it is not a superpower,
потому Да конечно не сверхдержава
correct And why, if the European Union is a
правильно А почему если Европейский союз
superpower Why shouldn't they be invited to
сверхдержава Почему их не приглашать на
peace talks about Ukraine, I
мирные переговоры про по Украине в
mean, And what kind of peace
смысле А что проходят какие-то мирные
talks are taking place on Ukraine Let's say soon
Переговоры по Украине Да допустим скоро
in Saudi Arabia, just look, look,
в Саудовской Аравии просто смотри
look, China, for example, China
какие-то смотри Китай например Китай
By the way, this minister of China said  Yes, he
Кстати да заявил этот министр Китая Да
said that Europe should be at the
сказал что Европа должна быть на
negotiations
переговоров
and what did he do after that? Tell me
и что после этого он сделал Скажите мне
please Nobody, there are no
пожалуйста Ничего никто не никаких
negotiations, you understand,
переговоров нету понимаешь
no negotiations. No, on
никаких переговоров Нет по
Ukraine, look how you see it. Negotiations on Ukraine without
Украине смотри как ты видишь Переговоры
Ukraine or
по Украине без Украины или
Russia, stop, you know, I don’t see negotiations
России стоп знаете я не вижу переговоров
on Ukraine without Ukraine or Russia, but
по Украине без Украины или России но
remember, let’s say, the
вспомните допустим
European summit. Yes, it was in my opinion in
саммит Европы Да это был по-моему
1923, who did they invite
двадцать третий год кого они позвали
Russia to? And what was discussed, peace.
Россию А что обсуждалось мирные
Negotiations on Ukraine, no peace, no,
Переговоры по Украине никакие мирны не
then peace negotiations. No, they weren’t discussed
нет тогда мирные переговоры Нет не
then, no. Then
обсуждались тогда нет Тогда Тогда
reparations were discussed. Then
обсуждались репарации Тогда обсуждались
reparations to Russia were discussed and assistance to
репарации России и обсуждались помощь
Ukraine was discussed. That’s all and everything is good, that’s right,
Украине вот и всё и всё хорошо правильно
peace negotiations, none, not even about peace
мирные переговоры никакие даже о мирных
negotiations, there’s no
переговорах никаких даже и не стоит даже
question and no one will, we won’t. Look, there won’t be
вопрос и никто не будет ми никаких не
any peace negotiations.
будет Смотри мирных переговоров не будет
This is a myth. They tell Russians about
это Миф это для русских рассказывают про
some kind of mines, American negotiations,
какие-то мины переговоры американских
like, and American negotiations, yes, like, that’s it, in
каже и американских да типа что вот
short, and Russians.
короче и русские
American Trump came, he needs to show
Американ Трамп пришёл ему надо показать
some kind of movement, Greenland, Panama, I’ll
Движуху какую-то там Гренландия панама
stop the war now. And that’s all. Yes, that
там сейчас остановлю войну И всё да то
is, the war, the Kursk region, as they soaked
есть война курскую область как мочили
it up.  and they will continue to wet
так и будут дальше мочить
Daro and showed Yes, that she is not a
Даро и показали Да что она всё она не
superpower, she cannot
сверхдержава она не может полгода
win back her part of the region for six months Well, that
отвоевать свою часть области Ну всё то
is, what kind of global geopolitics
есть про какие там геополитику мировую с
can we talk about with her, that's all Okay, good
ней можно говорить вот и всё Окей хорошо
In that case, you, by the same logic,
В таком случае вы по такой же логике
absolutely by yours, the whole of Europe,
абсолютно по вашей же целая Европа у
which has a GDP that is 10 times larger, is correct,
которой ВВП больше ну в 10 раз правильно
than Russia, cannot transfer such a
чем у России не может передать такое
quantity of weapons to win back a
количество оружия чтобы отвоевать
piece of the wound to at least some Europe,
кусочек раны хотя бы какой-нибудь Европе
you will explain, look, it is
вы объясню смотри
profitable for Russia to
выгодно чтобы Россия
wither on this front in the war and so that it
завяла на этом фронте в войне и чтобы
sends troops I do not die, is it correct
отправляла войска я не умирали правильно
Once again, so that Russia Yes, it
Ещё раз чтобы Россия Да военный
destroys Russia's military potential, yes, in Ukraine,
потенциал России уничтожал да в Украине
so that Russia does not jump on the Baltics, that's
чтобы Россия не прыгнула на прибалтику
all And what is happening with
вот и всё А что происходит с
Volkswagen, what is Wagen You know, a
фольксвагеном что Ваген Знаете мне мне 3
man told me about Volkswagen 3 months ago Well,
месяца назад мужик рассказывал про
now you tell me too
Фольксваген А ну теперь ещё ты расскажи
I'm not just interested
Не мне просто интересно
Tell me Yes, what when this news was,
Расскажи Да что когда эта новость была
let's say there 2 days ago, stop,
ну допустим там 2 дня назад условно стоп
stop, this news was told to me 3
стоп это эту новость мне рассказывали 3
months ago about Volkswagen, that the
месяца назад про Volkswagen что
store is closing I say no, but  I'm saying
закрывается зало Я говорю нет а я говорю
that 10 employees were fired there. This was
что там сколько 10 сотрудников уволили
told to me like this 3 months ago and this news has
рассказывали так а до тебя эта новость
reached you now. So what happened there? They
сейчас дошла Так и что там случилось
simply fired employees because they had to
Просто уволили сотрудников за того что
compete with China. Don't look where
конкурировать с Китаем не смотри де в
it is. Now look at how many
том теперь посмотри посмотри сколько в
factories were closed in Europe and transferred
Европе закры раз заводов и переносилась
to other economies, for example, to
в другие экономики к примеру в какую в
Indonesia or
Индонезию в во
Vietnam, the most important economy, where
Вьетнаме самая главная экономика кото
most of the factories
большая часть заводов больше процентов
were transferred, more than a percent, to the USA. Look again. The fact is
переносилась е США ещё раз смотри Дело в
that Europe and the
том что Европа и
USA have been transferring their
США уже лет 50 переносят свои
production facilities to countries with
производственные мощности в Страны с
low wages to poor
низкой оплачиваемый трудом в бедные
countries for 50 years now because of the pollution that was
страны потому что загрязнение что было
there,
там
cheap labor, that's all.
дешёвая рабочая сила там вот и всё
Engineers, engineers,
инженеры инженеры
look. As a result, look. As a result,
смотри В результате смотри В результате
Europe lives richer than Russia,
Европа живёт богаче да чем Россия у
which has AvtoVAZ. Yes, I don't
которой есть АвтоВАЗ Да я не
argue with Germany, whose population is
спорю Германия кото население сколько
roughly several times smaller. I've
там ну грубо говоря в раз меньше я в
been to Germany 10 times already. I'm a German, partly. Let's say they're moving
Германии был раз 10 уже ям немец отчасти
factories. You
вот иро пере заводы
know. The USA. In general, look.
допустим знаете США Да вообще смотри
Europe lives better. Wait, you just
Европа живёт лучше Подождите вы только
said absolutely.  another thing you
что говорили абсолютно другое вы
said is that Europe is moving factories to
говорили что Европа переносит заводы в
other countries, to poorer ones, so that they can
другие страны в более бедные чтобы было
pay less for
меньше платить за
labor, look again, as a result of all
труд ещё раз смотри В результате всего
this, Europe lives
этого Европа живёт
better than it did
лучше чем что чем жила
before, no, don't hang out,
раньше уже нет
economist, don't hang out, don't
экономист не Зависай не
hang out, I have a direct connection to the
Зависай у меня прямое подключение к
Internet, don't worry, three, I'm saying Europe
интернету переживай е три я говор Европа
now lives worse than it did before, than
сечас живёт хуже чем раньше раньше чем
when, for example, Well, let's say in 2019, I
когда допустим Ну допустим в 2019 году я
last came to Germany, Europe
приезжал последний раз в Германию Европа
now lives worse than in 2012, yes, the Armed Forces
сечас жит хуже чем в 2012 году да ВС
recorded better than in 2012, Dan is hanging out,
зафиксировали лучше чем в 2012 году Дани
economist will
зависают экономист
merge, economist,
сольётся о экономист
Internet, that's all,
Интернет да вот и всё
Hello, Hello, where are you
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
from, I'm from the Komi Republic,
откуда я с республики
Wow,
Вау
Syktyvkar, you guessed right, well, you didn't
Сыктывкар Да точно угадали Да ну не
guess,
угадали
and my father is from Ukhta, my mother is from Vorkuta, I am
А у меня отец из Ухты Мама из Воркуты я
Komi by nationality,
коми по национальности
by the way, seriously, are you Russian or
кстати серьёзно Да вы русский или
Komi? Well, I'm one of those who came here, yes, I'm kind of dumb, how does it
Коми Ну я из понаехавших Да я как бы
turn out, my father is not from
неме у меня как получается не отец из
Ukhta, and my mother is from a village near
Ухты А мама из деревни под
Vorkuta, yes  kome razn
воркутой Да коме рзн
it can be everything yes I understand I also have
она всё может быть да понял У меня ещё
this shirt of my father
вот эта рубаха отцовская
Well if there is a guard there maybe he was exiled no no
Ну если там вхт может быть он сосланный
He is Komi he is Komi Yes it
был нет нет Он Коми он Коми Да работал
turns out he worked Grandfather already worked in the
просто получается Дед уже работал в
city yes And Father was born there it is
городе да И Отец там родился
clear Well then fellow countrymen Yes it is nice to
понятно Ну значит земляки Да приятно
meet fellow countrymen you communicate about the World Cup
встретить земляков о ЧМ общаетесь
I wanted to say that I myself
я хотел сказать что у меня-то я-то сам
was born in the south in the Priluzsky
родился на юге в прилузском
district and the World Cup
районе а ЧМ
about I don’t know as a sofa Expert I can Talk about everything what do you
об не знаю как диван Эксперт могу О всём
think
говорить как считаете
CX pobvo
СХ поб во
Honestly I don’t have I don’t know at
Честно говоря у меня нет Я вот не знаю
least that you heard them
по крайней мере что вы их слышали знаете
you know Well I have a nephew of my friend
ти Ну у меня есть у моего друга
but he didn’t die he ended up in the hospital
племянник но он не погиб он в госпиталь
but what happened to him for sure I can’t
попал а вот что с ним точно я не могу
say And so I don’t
сказать А так не
know My father there it turns out a
знаю У моего отца там получается друг
childhood friend Igo was
детства иго
taken to the war then he ended up in the
бым забрали на войну то попал в
hospital he stepped on a mine and his
госпиталь ему он наступил на мину и ему
leg was injured and the crotch was shot
ногу повредила и промежность прострела
there in short an unpleasant thing and he lay in the hospital
там короче неприятная вещь и в госпитале
something was patched up his leg they recovered
отлежал ему что-то ногу залата отходили
him there for 9 months and they returned him again to
его там 9 месяцев и вернули снова на
front there mom wrote somewhere to
фронт там мама короче писала куда-то
Putin wrote to Shagu then what is this
Путину писала шагу тогда что как это
takti a child with such a wound falls on that
такти ребнок с таким ранением пает на ту
leg they sent put in an infantry fighting vehicle and in short they
ногу отправили посадили в БМП и короче
drove like that uh Ukrainian drone
погнали типа то э Дрон украинский
flew uh hit their MPSh the guys all
прилетел ээ влупил ихнюю мпш пацаны все
started to climb out run out and it turns out he was
начали вылазить выбегать а он получается
running the slowest and the Drone as you know like a
бежал самое медленно и Дрон как знаете
Predator catches up with the weakest that's
как как Хищник догоняет самого слабого
like a lion in the prairie when there
вот это как лев в прерии когда там
bison are running and the weak The bison lags behind and the
бизоны бегут и слабые Бизон отстаёт и
lions him then and in short Drone He just like
львы его тогда и короче Дрон Ему прямо
that well in the back in short flew apart I do
вот так ну в спину короче разлетелся
n't know this video also because mom
не знаю это видео ещ потому что мама
showed it sent it to
показывала присылала его
my father he showed the Ukrainians filmed
отцу моему он показывал украинцы сняли
this fight from another drone
ещё с другого дрона именно этот бой
and like there his body flew into two parts then he
и типа там разлетелось на две части его
tells mom mom they brought the
тела то маме говорит маме привезли в
body to Ukhta in a coffin they didn't allow to
Ухту тело в гробу гроб не разрешили
open the coffin they said that your Sanya is lying there
открывать сказали что там лежит ваш Саня
about
про
some guy from the military registration and enlistment office so that he had to
какой-то из военкомата чтобы он должен
record that they won't open the
был зафиксировать что они не откроют
coffin and like  that's it, well, in short, mom gave
гроб и типа всё ну короче мама дала
money to at least look at her son, they
деньги чтобы хотя бы посмотреть на сына
open it, and there's only the
открывают А там только нижняя часть
lower part, the lower part is lying there, that is, they found it or were
нижняя часть лежит то есть они нашли или
able to pick it up there, it's only the legs
там смогли подобрать Это только ноги
here and a piece of the body and that's it, and the
сюда и кусок тела и всё А Верхне так и
upper part is still missing, that is, somewhere else, maybe they can slip it to someone to bury the upper part, but I
подсунуть похоронить его верхнюю часть
don't know why, well, maybe someone is
а зачем не знаю Ну может ти кто-то как
missing, Be is numbered, yes, I'll
пропавший Бе числи Да его вторую
throw off the other half of the sleigh, so this is
половину сани прохо скину ска вот это
your Vasya, don't open the coffin and
ваш Вася не открывайте гроб и всё
bury him,
хороните
look, if a person has disappeared without truth,
смотрите если человек без исти пропал то
then probably they won't pay anything to mom, but
тогда наверно маме не заплатят ничего а
if he hasn't disappeared without truth, then probably they'll pay something anyway, I know, then I know,
если он как бы не пропал без исти то
it's Vasya Prokhorov who will help
тогда знат Это Вася Прохоров выручит
someone out, some mom, some mom, maybe, but maybe, you
кого-то какую-то маму какую Может и так
know, maybe I now
а вот может знаете может это я теперь
understand, yes, it turns out that the commander, well, the
понял да это получается что командир Ну
guys understand that if they
ребята понимают что если этого с поля
couldn't get him from the battlefield, his relatives will
боя не смогли достать его родственники
now have to wait there for a year, and that's not it, but
теперь будут там год ждать и не это а
they took half of Prokhorov's sleigh and
так они взяли половину сани Прохорова
sent him as Sanya  Prokhorov was
отправили как Саню Прохорова половину
sent half as someone else from the regiment
отправили как кого-то другого из полка
Well, that's what I can assume
Ну это я так могу предположить Может
Maybe I'm logical Yes, it's logical that he was
быть я вот это логично Да это логично
missing in action
получается чтобы так пропавший безвести
And so one for half and all the payments
А так один за пол и все выплаты
Get it, that is, the guys at the front know
Получи то есть пацаны на фронте знают
what they're doing Well, yes, they kind of help each other out
что делают Ну да они типа друг друга
so that the families get it Well, yeah,
выручают как бы чтобы семьи получили Ну
damn, and I think that mom was sent
да блин а я думаю что мам прислали
half of the
половину
sa there was nothing to send That's why they
са там нечего было прислать Поэтому
say that the coffin wasn't
говорят что гроб не
opened coffins came from Afghanistan,
откры гробы приходили с Афганистана
for example, there were also such
например там тоже тоже такие были
sealed coffins that no one
запаянный гробы которые никто не
opened and zinc humps Yes, there was one like that too Yes,
открывал да цинковые горбы да вот вот
as they say, a pig in a poke And
был да это как говорится кота в мешке А
this is
это
called a Russian in a coffin Yes, damn,
называется как русский в гробу Да блин
not at all Well, then it's not only Russians
вобще не Ну тогда не только русские
now I'm saying there was a pig in a poke
сейчас я же говорю там было кота в мешке
And that's what it turns out to be Yes And listen, how it
А это получается да А слушай как
turns out, for example Well, why are these
получается вот например Ну за что эти
guys dying in
ребята погибают в
Ukraine Well, for the interests of Russia, probably And
Украине Ну за интересы России наверное А
what are such interests that they die in
в чём такие интересы чтобы они умерли в
another
другой
country Well, I don't know why wars
стране Ну вот я не знаю для чего войны
even happen Once upon a time some
вообще наступают вот когда-то там
king didn't like
какому-то королю типа не понравился
another king  his wife didn't like it
другой король его жена не понравилась
or on the contrary liked it well yes there was such a thing
или наоборот понравилась ну да было
especially in Greece there were so many of them
такое вот особенно в Греции тако много
Okay, reis the guys in Russia go to
было Так ладно реис пацаны в России идут
die in a foreign country exactly So exactly the
умирать в чужую страну точно Так точно
same as before what's the interest what's the
так же как и раньше в чём интерес в чём
interest of Russia for them to die in another
интерес России чтобы они умерли в другой
country Well the interest is even in the fact that they
стране Ну вот интерес даже в том чтобы
still listen to the Russians Well the fact that
всё-таки прислушались к россий Ну то что
Russia has its own interests look there are
У России есть свои интересы вот смотрите
interests for example Germany has interests
есть интересы например там у Германии Да
Yes the United States of America has interests who
есть у Соединённых Штатов Америки на
Germany is attacking just a second I'm
кого Германия нападает секундочку я вам
telling you So Russia also has its own
так говорю Вот и у России тоже есть свои
interests pun
интерес пун там
spoke there in the year or some year there
выступил году или каком-то там году
said Guys let's sit down and talk and
сказал Ребята давайте сядем поговорим и
Well about our security yours our
Ну о нашей безопасности вашей нашей
common They told him Listen guy Go to
общей Ему сказали Слушай парень Иди
hell we know what we want ourselves And what are
лесом мы сами знаем что мы хотим И что
we going to do
мы будем
wrong the war is already going on just a second
делать не так война уже с идт секундочку
I'm talking to you
я Вам
about and so They told him go to hell what do
про и вот Ему сказали что иди лесом
you have any
то что тебя У тебя есть какие-то
interests we are not interested in this we are
интересы нас это не интересует нас
only interested in that we are all the war has
интересует только что мы всё вот война
started Well that's right Well it's logical
началась Ну это правильно Ну это логично
that Well look everyone is interested in their own
что Ну смотри каждого интересуют свои
interests that's right And why did you attack
интересы это правильно А зачем вы напали
someone else's  country set aside interests
на чужую страну отставить интересы
diplomatic economic Okay
дипломатические экономически Хорошо
okay I'll tell you
хорошо я вам
Wait war is a continuation of
Подождите война - это продолжение
diplomacy only in other ways No no this is This is
дипломатии только другими способами Нет
bye wait Wait once once we
нет это Это бай подожди Подождите раз
couldn't agree
раз не смогли
our so to speak politicians then it
договориться наши так скажем политики то
means the matter enters into a free everything that is
значит дело вступают в волен всё то есть
I understand correctly this is everywhere I
я правильно понимаю это это везде я
understand correctly if I want to buy a house
правильно понимаю если я хочу купить дом
and can't agree with the owner I
и не могу договориться с собственником Я
start to climb on him with a gun so uh No not
начинаю на него лезть с пистолетом так э
really Why do you fall under the
Нет не совсем Почему вы попадаете под
Criminal Code immediately like that and here it
Уголовный кодекс сразу же вот так и тут
turns out yes because I I Priest under
получается да потому что я я Прист под
what code under what you yes you
какой кодекс под какой вы да вы
violate the
нарушаете статут
UN statute what UN statute yes about aggression against
ООН какой статут ООН да про агрессию на
another state you can't commit
другое государство нельзя делать
aggression against another state And you
агрессию против другого государства А вы
know that there are states that Hali
знаете что есть государства которые Хали
on these here
на вот эти вот
Old look also absolutely look also
Старо смотри так же абсолю смотри так же
as there is a bandit who sneezed on the
как есть бандит который чихал на
Criminal Code and goes to kill someone
Уголовный кодекс и идёт убивать кого-то
Yes and Russia that is well we agree stop once
Да так и Россия то есть ну согласны стоп
again we agree that there are sovereign
ещё раз согласны что есть суверенные
states and Russia Yes as a member of the UN it
государства и Россия Да как член ООН она
recognizes the UN statute Well probably yes No
признаёт статут ООН Да ну наверное да Не
probably but it recognizes a member  UN it
наверно а признаёт она член ООН она
recognizes the UN statute Otherwise it wouldn't exist it would have
признаёт статут ООН Иначе она бы не была
left this organization it
она бы вышла из этой организации она
recognizes the UN statute the UN statute says
признаёт статут ООН статут ООН говорит
if you want I can read it to you now
если хотите могу зачитать вам сейчас
open it word for word
открыть прямо дословно
read it that every sovereign
зачитать что каждое суверенное
state Yes has the right to determine
государство Да вправе само определять
its own policy Yes to join or not
свою политику Да вступать или не
join any blocs and so no
вступать в какие-то блоки и так ни одно
sovereign state should be
суверенное государство не должно быть
subjected to attack by another
подвергнуто да нападению другого
aggression aggression of another
агрессии агрессии там другого
state and so on Yes that is
государства и так дальше Да вот то есть
directly condemns
прямо осуждает
further in the UN resolution the
дальше в резолюции ООН осуждена
attack of Russia on Ukraine is condemned also yes that
нападение России на Украину также да то
is
есть
Russia There is a
Россия Есть
state wait one more time
государство подожди ещ раз ещё раз
wait one more time then look in the World Cup the point is already on
подожди значит смотри в ЧМ суть уже
let's be on "you" we seem to be
на давай на ты будем мы вроде там
peers with strangers Then I will be on "you" I
ровесники с незнаком чело Тогда я буду
already recognized you I will be
на ты я вас уже узнал Я буду
naked we won't come to an agreement with you wait it is
наг т с вами не договоримся подожди это
in my interests in my interests to
в моих интересах в моих интересах
call you "naty" if you call
называть тебя наты ес если вы будете
me "naty" I will go further you will get
меня наты называть я пойду дальше
scared everything goodbye you run away
испугаешься всё до свидания убегаешь
how gentle to date here
какой нежен ко дату тут можно
you can call me "you"
на что ты меня на Ты
I am such an intellectual yes in general  have
назвал я интеллигент такой да вообще
you already gotten too bold Yes even naty this is too much for you like
оборзели уже Да даже наты это к вам
subscription to
лайк подписка ко
Hello where are
Здравствуйте откуда
you from Stavropol you are from Krasnodar
Вы Ставрополя вы с Краснодарского
region Why is the location Ukraine
края Почему стоит локация Украина
moved to Ukraine And in the sense that I lived in
переехал в Украину А в смысле жил в
Krasnodar moved there and became a
Краснодаре переехал туда да и стал
patriot
патриотом
yes VDA you are
да вда за укра
not fighting for Ukraine in the Russian Volunteer
не воюешь в русском Добровольческой
Corps in the RDK We are also luring from
корпусе в РДК Мы переманивает тоже с
Russia from Krasnodar Yes, I also have
России с Краснодара Да тоже у меня
football fans who have now switched over
футбольные фанаты сейчас перешли
a lot Normally we are patriots of Russia
много Нормально мы патриоты России
against Putin's I understand that you can't do
против путинской я понимаю что вы там не
anything there We also have guys who
можете ничего У нас тоже ребята которые
stayed in Russia they can't even go to a rally
остались в России они там даже На митинг
there damn lawlessness mom
не могут выйти там блин беспредел у мамы
18,000
18.000
ns so Why did you go there what
нси так А почему ты туда ушёл что
prompted you because it is a free
сподвигла потому что это свободная
country because the only Ukraine
страна потому что единственная Украина
we consider we
мы рассматриваем мы русский
consider the Russian Volunteer Corps as
добровольческий корпус рассматриваем как
Ukraine as the only instrument
Украину как единственный инструмент
for the destruction of the Russian Federation
для разрушения Российской Федерации вот
this Kremlin
этого кремлёвского
regime You know that they will destroy Ukraine
режима Ты знае что они разрушат Украина
Why look The Russian Empire was
Почему смотри Российскую империю
destroyed
разрушили
since you know history you know who
раз ты же знаешь историю ты знаешь кто
destroyed it how it was destroyed Well, that's right
разрушил как разрушил Ну правильно
Gorbachev with Yeltsin with the help of all sorts of
Горбачёв с Ельциным с помощью всяких
Ukrainians, Lithuanians And so on and so forth, the same thing is
украинцев литовцев И так дальше сейчас
being done Look, it was not different
тоже самое делается Смотри не по-другому
And now it's the same
былов А сейчас так же
Samora, all
самора все вот
these Americans were put there, the
эти Американ поставили
Americans put it there a little differently,
американцы поставили там чуть по-другому
everything was no, no Well, the same thing on purpose The thing is that
было всё нет не Ну то же специально Дело
look The point is what's the matter The point is that it
в том что смотри Суть в чём дело Суть в
destabilizes the situation so that
том что шатает ситуацию так чтобы у
Russia has no army left No
России не осталось армии не Осталось
armored vehicles left No missiles left yes In order to be
бронетехники Не осталось ракет да Для
able to
того чтобы можно было сделать
dismember it into different states
расчленение её на разные государства
Because when the Soviet Union was
Потому что когда Советский Союз
dismembered Yes, it turned out that they had nuclear weapons,
расчленили Да оказалось у тех ядерка у
those nuclear weapons were still running around, then for 3 years
тех ядерка ещё бегали потом 3 года
they asked for the nuclear weapons to be postponed And now
просили чтобы ядерку отложили А сейчас
everything is working out, Russia, what are you preparing already You
всё получается Россию че уже готови Ты
saw how much army Kadyrov has, yes And
видел как сколько армии у Кадырова да И
how much weapons there were in the nineties, there
сколько оружия такого в девяностых даже
weren't even in Chechnya Well, again, you see
не было в Чечне Ну опять же видишь Они
How they fight on the Russian side now
как воюют на русской стороне сечас так
they don't fight Look, here we are, the RDK
они не воюют Смотри что вот мы РДК
How many Russian guys were taken prisoner, we
Сколько русских пацанов брали в плен
say, and where are the Kadyrovites, they say They are
говорим а где кадыровцы они говорят Они
standing, in short, 15 km away  from the front And they
короче стоят Там за 15 км от фронта А
take us, like conscripts and such, they
нас типа срочников и таких берут они сем
hang seven medals on Russian guys,
медалей вешают русских пацанов
they drive them away, not that they know 15, they are
гонят они не то чтобы знаят 15 они
far away Look,
далеко
I dragged this one, we went to the Kursk
Смотри я вон притащил мы в курскую
region when we entered Yes, they took the number off the
область когда заходили Да номерок с
car, well, the car is now driving
машины сняли ну машина сейчас катается
there to deliver ammunition, but there
там для подвоза боекомплекта во ни
was not a single Kadyrovite there, not a single one,
одного кадыровца не было ни одного там
this Lotel guy was filming videos In
этот что-то лотел один снимал видосы
short, all Russian guys are simple
Короче всё русские пацаны простые
conscripts now, some, in short, some were
срочники сейчас часть короче часть
exchanged, and some said they wanted to
обменяли их а часть сказали что хотят
stay, like, and fight in the RDC, they are fighting
остаться типа и воевать в РДК воюют
now in the RDC Damn, the fighters are
сейчас в РДК Блин вообще бойцы
like
как
guys And what are those, what kind of privileges does the RDC have
пацаны А что там что за привилегий РДК
Well, first of all, they treat people like people Yes,
ну во-первых относятся как к людям Да
because the Russian army, we look at
потому что Российская армия мы смотрим
these guys, there is hazing, in short,
вот эти пацаны там дедовщина короче
some kind of bullying, the commander is like
какие-то издевается командир Как
ska, damn, normal In short, how do you
ска блин нормально Короче как человеку
treat a person The fighting brotherhood of Rus' is generally
относится Братство боевое Руси вообще
cool
круто
Look Here, we have I, I [ __ ], I am from Krasnodar
Смотри Вот у нас я я сри я с Краснодара
Yes, we also have a guy from Moscow, also
Да у нас ещё парень с Москвы тоже
Russian Yes  there are from St. Petersburg from all
русский Да есть с Питера со всех с
different ones that Stavropol there is no one from
разных что ставропольских нет никого из
Stavropol No there is Mineralnye Vody from
Ставрополя Нет есть Минеральных Вод с
Pyatigorsk there is from there there is
Пятигорска есть оттуда
myself Just Dukov I thought to tell
есть сам Просто дуков я думал сказать
you that one
тебе что
hundred b Krasava in short then maybe we will also like
ста б Красава короче то может тоже типа
find a place here No no they won't
тут найдём те место
take I don't understand Well that's it Yes Toda they won't take
Да не не возьмут Не Поня Ну такое Да
you in the sense we won't take
Тода у вас не возьмут смысле по не
not if he's creepy we won't take And
возьмём не если стрёмный не возьмём А
so like and a lot of guys you understand but
так типа и много ребят понимаешь
you say creepy or what Well
по а стрёмный ты говоришь или как Ну
if he's creepy yes they won't take And so I'll
если стрёмный да то не возьмут А так я
tell you what we have a lot of guys from
тебе вот что скажу у нас много ребят из
Russia crossing they go through Georgia so they
России переходит едут через Грузию так
go they come in like yes Through other countries
едут заходят типа да Через другие страны
through Turkey they come in because well
через Турцию заезжают потому что ну
directly through Belarus or Russia right now the Armed Forces are at
напрямую через белору или Россию тут же
war So yes Yes not for me you know how it's
ВС война Так что да Да не мне мне знаешь
even easier for me to come in than for
как мне ещё проще зайти чем
them to swim across the river I'm already there you are some kind of
им речку переплыть Я уже там ты какой-то
military man Well yes a
военный Ну
contract soldier
да контрактник
mobilized contract soldier yes and it's
мобилизованный контрактник да а это
true that In short you now
правда что Короче у вас сейчас там
showed the wounded there a little bit nearby On
показывали раненых чуть-чуть подле На
crutches  they send too damn to these you
костылях отправляют тоже блин в эти
know more how demoralization goes
это больше знаешь как идёт деморализация
there is no such thing I don't see Honestly
нету такого я и не вижу Вот честно слово
I don't see that the guys were filming that
я не вижу то то чтоб пацаны снимали что
like donkeys are already delivering
типа ослами уже подвозят
ammunition donkey for fun they gave not that well that's just
боекомплект ишака для прикола дали не
kidding
это это ну это прикололись
I've been fighting since 2012 And who are you
я с двенадцатого года как бы воюю А ты
by
кто по
nationality Rukiy Russian since what
национальности рукий русский с какого
year have you been fighting
года ты воюешь
2012 and what in 2012
двенадцатого года а что в двенадцатом
Where in 2012 here not here but where did the
Где в двенадцатом здесь не здесь а где е
dude
чувака
start fighting in Syria
начинал в Сирии
Syria and Ukrainian
воевал Сирия а украинского
and Listen I you know what I don't understand why
а Слушай я вот знаешь что не пойму зачем
in short
короче
uh Russia just takes Russian guys and
ээ Россия берёт просто русских пацанов и
throws them like meat in huge quantities like
кидает как мясо в огромных количествах
that into assaults just Toto what if there are
вот так в штурмы просто Тото что если
these hazelnuts Kuko hazelnuts Why
есть эти орешники Куко орешники Почему
not bang And that's it And stop the war
не жахнуть И всё И остановить войну Вот
Honestly I don't know that's why I put you know
честно не знаю поэтому я поставил знаешь
Ukraine just to talk to people
Украину чтоб просто поговорить с людьми
what's going on there well that is look I don't
что как у них там ну то есть смотри я не
understand Putin Yeah uh wanted to capture
понимаю Путин Да ээ захотел захватить
Kyiv it didn't work out and now it turns out
Киев не получилось и теперь получается
He's been like you for 3 years  guys How you
Он 3 года вот вас таких пацанов Как вы
drive not me you know how it is
гоняет не у меня это знаешь как это у
I already have work going
меня уже работа пошла
First not that and then it's work you
Первый не то а потом это работа ты
treat as To work And as for the
относишься как К работе А насчёт вот
guys to you Bach you mean those
пацанов ко ты Бах вот имеешь в виду те
directions Yes everything and now it's like the same Look how the
направления Да все и сейчас также типа
Ukrainians show
получается Вон как показывают украинцы
like it was that they took in the Kursk
типа было что взяли поставили в Курской
region put red flags on tanks and went
области на танки красные флаги и пошли
through a minefield damn the whole column was
по минному полю блин всю колонну
dismantled Russian
разобрали русскую
I
Я
saw in the World Cup A joke yes then the commander has to
видел в ЧМ Прикол да пото командиру
report that he is doing something Yes
отчитаться что он что-то делает
I have never seen anything like that let's say
Да не такого я не встречал допустим вот
we don't have such a thing
у нас такого нету
z vi as they
з ви как
show truth untrue also you
показывают правда неправда так же само
know how our news is played And
знае как наши новости крутят А ты на
what
каком
direction are you in Zaporozhye
направлении Запорожье
understood We are RDK we are
понял Мы РДК мы
from the Kremlin Damn we can't do it you see
от Кремля Блин у
you too
нас не получается видишь у вас тоже
Liberate everything is working out just right yes
Освободи всё как раз получается да
Listen we What was our task yes Our
Слушай мы Наша задача какая была да Наша
task was to go and occupy the Kursk region
задача была зайти занять курскую область
in order to show the whole world that
для того чтобы показать всему миру что
Putin cannot control his
Путин не может контролировать свою
territory Because when Putin fought
территорию Потому что когда Путин воевал
on the territory of Ukraine yes like there they
на территории Украины да типа там
thought that Well Ukraine cannot yes And
считали что Ну вот Украина не может да А
when  we went in but first we tried
когда зашли но мы сначала пробовали вот
Belgorod region Yes, in
Белгородскую область Да
short, there it was so
там короче там так
good in Kursk, they went in there and
в курскую вообще хорошо зашли там и
Americans went in, like Germans and
американцы заходили типа и немцы и
French, in short,
французы
who hasn't
короче там просто короче кто только не
gone in there, these crazy Americans
заходил уже эти отжига американцы так
took pictures like this Pyaterochka store in
фоткались типа этот магазин Пятёрочка в
Sudzha Yes, the Americans, in short, the block was filmed by an
Судже Да американцы короче блок снимали
American and
американец был а
not, not the Ukrainians And so, like, for themselves, they filmed it on an
не не то украинцы А так типа для себя на
American blog, in short,
американский блог снимали короче гово
look what kind of stuff they feed Russians, they
смотрите каким короче кормят россиян они
say They open it there, look, reads
говорят Они открывают там смотрит читает
this composition, in short, some kind of GMO, and like,
этот состав короче какой-то ГМО ещё типа
they were just laughing there, takes it, takes out cheese,
там они просто угорали берёт достаёт сыр
in short, and this cheese, As he says, like
короче а этот сыр Как говорит как
some kind of plasticine He even spat, damn, he
пластилин какой-то Он аж плевался блин
says that we in America should have such food,
говорит чтобы у нас в Америке такая еда
our pigs don't eat that Yes,
была у нас свиньи такой не едят
like, subscribe, comment,
Да лайк подписка комент
so let's move on Hello, Hello,
так Поехали дальше Здравствуйте
where are you from, St. Petersburg? You are from
Здравствуйте Вы откуда с Питера Вы из
Krasnodar But I live in Poland, in
Краснодара Но живу в Польше в
Krakow What topics do you talk about, war?
Кракове На какие темы общаетесь война
How do you feel about the fact that our
Как вы относитесь к тому что наш
president Donald Tusk said that Europe
президент Дональд Туск заявил что Европе
needs to prepare to
надо готовиться к тому чтобы в Украину
send its military
отправить свой военный
contingent to Ukraine? No, no  I know who
контингент Да не я знаю кто какая
will be what Poland well look for yourself they are asking
Польша будет ну посмотри сам просят
in short 200,000 Yes it is necessary or how much of
короче 200.000 Да надо или сколько
this contingent to send yes who is
отправить этого контингента да кто
asking Well Zelensky there Wants there gender not
просит Ну Зеленский там Хочет там пол не
Zelensky there he calls these
Зеленский там он от балды называет эти
numbers out of nowhere this is such a thing here really really
цифры это ж такое тут реально реально
what contingent is needed there I have no idea
какой контингент там нужен вот я понятия
I am not a military man for a discount we will take
не имею Я не военный на скидку возьмём
Well there 200 or 100,000
Ну там 200 или 100.000
Well well 100 Yes let's take the minimum there
Да ну 100 Да давай возьмём минимуму там
1700 km less straight Well for example So they will
на 1700 км меньше пря Ну например Так
smoke there After 50 km each
там курить будут там Через 50 км каждый
there are five
там по пять
people look each one must be paid a
человек смотри каждому надо платить по
five Well Zelensky well this is adequate
Пятёрке Ну зелене ну это адекватно
simply at least well 100,000 by 5000
просто хотя бы ну 100.000 на 5000
how much is that half a billion a
умножаем сколько это полмиллиарда в
month Well how do
месяц Ну как бы как
you like it cheaper than spending later on a
тебе это дешевле чем тратить потом на
war on your territory Yes what war
войну на своей территории Да какая война
on your territory Who will
на своей территории Кто там ядерную
go to war there
войну полезет
Listen after the Kursk region
Слушай после Курской области про ядерную
you can forget about a nuclear war And what is there in the Kursk
войну можно забыть А что там в Курской
region Well that the territory of Russia
области Ну что территорию России
was captured and Russia a nuclear  war not
захватили а Россия ядерную войну не на
there like 500 square that's not the point that's
там типа 500 квадратных это суть же не в
not the point that's true The point is
том суть же не в том правда Суть в том
that the territory of Russia was captured and
что территорию России да захватили и
Russia didn't
Россия никак не
respond in any way I mean it responded at 3,000
ответила В смысле ответила она по 3.000
km per month captures again look at the
км к в месяц захваты ещё раз смотри
territory of Russia was captured they are shelling with
территорию России захватили обстреливают
NATO weapons and Russia didn't
натовский оружием и Россия не не
respond at
ответила
all Well But isn't the answer that for
ничего Ну А разве не ответ то что на
half a year at 3,000 km
полгода по 3.000 км захватывает
square is captured per month 3,000 square km for
квадратных в месяц 3.000 ква км по
half a year Well yes that's not much but but you have
полгода Ну да это немного но но у вас-то
500 again again again again 3,000 MT in
500 ещё раз ещё раз ещё раз 3.000 МТ в
half a year per month per month Yes
полгода в месяц в месяц Да стабильность
summer stability can you imagine what 3,000
лета ты представляешь что такое 3.000
KKM is how much
ККМ сколько на сколько
is 3,000
это 3.000
m well it's hard to say now
м ну сложно так сечас сказать
Well something should be squared Well what
Ну что-то должно быть в квадрате Ну что
should be squared to
должно быть в квадрате чтобы
get 50 to 50 And there's still some
получить получается 50 на 50 И ещё там
left there Well or Well how much is there 50
остаётся Да ну или Ну сколько вот там 50
square that will be 2500
квадра это будет 2500
Well how well are you your Well  50 by 60 3000 km is a
Да ну как ну ты сво Ну 50 на 60 3000 км
rectangle 50 km by 60
- это прямоугольник 50 км на 60
km Well, look, stop, stop, stop,
км Ну ну это смотри стоп стоп стоп это
look, it's the same as if on a line
Смотри это всё равно что на линии длиной
300 km long they advanced only 10 km
300 км продвинулись на 10 км
I'm not saying that this is simply
всего я не говорю что это прямо
colossal I don't even know Well, I do
колоссально это я даже не знаю Ну я даже
n't even know where you get these figures from, yes,
не знаю откуда вы эти цифры да такие
like yes, but e The point is The point is
берёте типа да но э Суть в том Суть в
that you can't Yes, if you have such a
том что вы не можете Да если у вас такие
frantic pace of advancement Why aren't they
бешеные темпы продвижения Почему их нету
in the Kursk
в Курской
region Well, they dug in well Well, there's the
области Ну окопались хороше Ну там вот
same Chasov Yar, all the others there are also like, you
тот же Часов Яр все остальные там тоже
can't throw bombs there,
как бы вот туда бомбы нельзя кидать
let's say, probably I wonder what Chasov
допустим наверно Интересно а что Часов
Yar, how long have you been trying to take that Ir hour Well, for
Яр сколько вы тот час Ир пробуете взять
a long time I'm saying that it's been a year Wait a year
Ну долго Я же говорю то что год уже
about that hour You say Yes,
Подожди уже год про тот час Говорите Да
they just put it there No,
просто ва там поставили там не Не ну
look You say that it's been an AVR hour, you
посмотри Ты же говоришь что час АВР вы
say it's been a year already I don't know And you see it's
говорите год год уже не знаю А видишь
burnt Well, tell me if you're promoting it
подгорел Ну скажи если вы продвигаемую
and they didn't even take it,
а его не взяли даже
of course Well, others  settlements with look
конечно Ну другие поселения с смотри
how long have you been from the
сколько вы уже год находитесь от
sentry Yar for a year Well, you've dug in really well 8 years
часового Яра Ну сильно окопались 8 лет
fortified how long have you been from the
укрепляли сколько вы находитесь от
sentry Yar I don't know well we've been in the Kursk
часова Яра Я не знаю хорошо в Курской
region for half a year we haven't
области мы находимся полгода мы не
dug in really well like 8 years Why don't you
окопались сильно как 8 лет Почему вы не
take the Kursk region in half a month You ca
заберёте курскую область за полмесяца
n't throw bombs there in the SSS
бомбы Туда нельзя кидать в ссз кидать Ну
throw Well the fact that there are civilians there too, as if they don't throw bombs there like on Pokrov And in the sentry Yar there are no civilians Well there are ours like Well I think and that is, you can throw bombs at Ukrainian civilians Yes Our task is to evacuate them, right stop stop stop I
правильно стоп стоп стоп Я правильно
understood correctly that is, they make peace on Ukrainians for
понял то есть на украинских мир ются за
words no No well you yourself said that
слова не Не ну ты же сам сказал что в
you don't throw bombs in Kursk You're even laughing that you
Курск не Кида ты аж сам Смеёшься что
caught it with yes that is, you don't
поймал со да то есть в Курск вы не
throw bombs at Kursk because there are
кидаете бомбы потому что там мирные
your civilians And in Bakh look in Bakh there in
жители ваши А в Бах смотри в Бах там в
Donetsk in short then everything can be thrown
Донецк короче дальше всё можно кидать
there Ukraine should be evacuated no don't look that  there
там Укра эвакуировать не не смотри то
is cool cool you just
есть круто круто ты ты только что
admitted that Russia is killing
признал что Россия убивает мирных
civilians on the territory of Ukraine and not
жителей на территории Украины и не
worrying about it
париться об этом
well done you are great Look you are great you are
молодец ты молодец Смотри ты молодец ты
for me You did a very beautiful yes you
для меня Ты сделал очень красивый да ты
blurted out and then already understood Yes what was it necessary to
ляпнул и уже понял потом Да что надо
think first yes from the masses yes no no yes yes
было сначала думать да от мас да нене не
you really admitted you admitted
да да ты реально ты признал ты признал
that the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation is
что Минобороны Российской Федерации
killing civilians in Ukraine people
убивает мирных жителей в Украине народ
we finally got from these Russians The
мы наконец-то получили от этих россиян
truth that Yes they were afraid to say
Ту правду которую Да они боялись сказать
in our country There was a brave man who is not afraid of
у нас Нашёлся смелый который не боится
persecution by the FSB and said that Russia is
преследования ФСБ и рассказал что Россия
not dropping bombs on the Kursk region
не скидает бомбы на курскую область
because there are Russian civilians
потому что там российские мирные жители
And it is dropping bombs on settlements in Ukraine
А на поселение в Украине скидывает бомбы
because there are Ukrainian civilians
потому что там украинские мирные жители
man really thank you very much
мужик реально тебе огромное спасибо
I really want to thank you Because
я реально хочу тебя поблагодарить Потому
you are a Svetoch you
что ты Светоч ты
will be propaganda for all these
будешь пропагандой для всех вот этих ных
Russian mo where he ran away hung
российских мо скуда
up for all the Russian bath
убежал завис для всех российских ванных
masses we will show that the people of
масс мы будем показывать что народ
Russia are waking up the people of Russia are no longer
России просыпается народ России уже не
embarrassed to talk about the crime of
стесняется говорить про преступление
this Russian regime in killing
этого российского режима по убийству
civilians of Ukraine and we will send this to
мирных жителей Украины и отправим это в
Europe  translate into other languages ​​Glory to
Европу переведём на другие языки Слава
Ukraine Thank you subscribe to my
Украине Спасибо подпишись на мий
Instagram I don't know why it's for you why else
Instagram Я не знаю для чого це тоб для
you should watch it This is my
чого ще тоб там дивитись на ось Цей мий
face But for you it's one two or three
фейс Але для тебе це один два або три
clicks But you try me and I will say Wow I have a
клика Але ты тримае мене и я буду каза
lot of followers and I
Вау в мене там Купа фолловер и в мене
will be in a great mood to do New
буде класный настрой щоб робити Нови
cool video letter on my Instagram Popik
крут вдео пись на мий Instagram Попик
Andr that's it
Андр вот
I'm
так давай я тебя
waiting for you N
чекаю N